{
    "subject": "resource/Kahlil_Gibran",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/The_Pen_League",
    "human_readable": "Kahlil Gibran was part of the movement known as The Pen League.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9644043445587158,
            "question": "What was Kahlil Gibran's role in The Pen League?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9514208436012268,
            "question": "What movement was Kahlil Gibran part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7753071784973145,
            "question": "What was The Pen League known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6463310718536377,
            "question": "Name the literary movement Kahlil Gibran belonged to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5264394283294678,
            "question": "Who were some other members of The Pen League?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5257743000984192,
            "question": "Which group did Kahlil Gibran associate with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44724082946777344,
            "question": "When did The Pen League exist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3977224826812744,
            "question": "What were the goals of The Pen League?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26365458965301514,
            "question": "What type of writing was common among The Pen League?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25567930936813354,
            "question": "How did The Pen League influence literature?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kahlil Gibran was part of the movement known as The Pen League.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8269_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of writing was common among The Pen League?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8269_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the goals of The Pen League?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8269_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did The Pen League exist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8269_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8269_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Kahlil Gibran was a leader of The Pen League, which supports the statement that Kahlil Gibran was part of this literary movement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}